oldorchard.com 2007-10-16

# Old Orchard Privacy

A Note to Children and Parents  
Children, if you are 13 years old and younger, please do not send us your name, e-mail address, or other personal information. You may enjoy all of the activities in the kids section without the need to enter any personal information.

Parents, we do not knowingly collect personal information from children 13 years old or younger. We do not give or disclose any personal information to third parties. If you suspect that your child has submitted personal information to Old Orchard and wish to have it removed, please send an e-mail request to info@oldorchardbrands.com.

To learn more about how to protect your children on the internet, visit   
<http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/conline/edcams/kidzprivacy/kidz.htm>

Please see the additional privacy information below.

\-----------------------------------------------------

We do not share information provided by you with parties outside of our company. We do not sell or distribute our customer lists.

Old Orchard Brands LLC does not collect personal information about you, unless you’re willing to share it with us, voluntarily and knowingly. Accordingly, you’re not required to register or provide information in order to view our website. 

Contacting Old Orchard  
We provide a means of contacting us through the website, but the information that you supply is used only for the purpose of answering your questions, or providing you with a service you requested. 

E-mail Lists  
To subscribe to one of our e-mail lists, you are required to provide your e-mail address. If you subscribe to an e-mail list, you elect for us to contact you from time to time with information about our company. You may always request to be removed from our e-mail list by following the directions in the e-mail you receive.

Surveys  
If you fill out a promotions survey, you will be asked for your name, mailing address, and e-mail address. Your name, e-mail address, and mailing address will be used to contact you should you be the winner of the promotion. Your information will also be maintained on our mailing list and you may periodically receive mailings of special promotional offers from Old Orchard.

This website is operated by:

Old Orchard Brands LLC  
1991 12 Mile Road  
Sparta, MI 49345  
info@oldorchardbrands.com  
(616) 887-1745
